Guide to the University Of Montana (System) Records 1915-1958
Montana Historical Society
- Subject Files
  - #225 Commencements, convocations, and public exercises (Northern Montana College), 1929-1957 (Box-folder 16 / 8-9)
  - #227-5 Hughes' Community Civics Supplement, 1921 (Box-folder 16 / 10)
  - #234-9 Montana Historical Society, 1920-1949 (Box-folder 16 / 11)
  - #236-B Moving pictures and lantern slides [audiovisual education], 1922-1954 (Box-folder 16 / 12)
  - #238 Newspaper clippings and news notes, 1920-1945 (Box-folder 16 / 13-18)
  - #238-2 News Notes (State College), 1920-1931 (Box-folder 16 / 19-20)
  - #238-3 Newspaper clippings and news notes (Normal College), 1920-1946 (Box-folder 16 / 21)
  - #238-4 Press releases (School of Mines), 1930-1935 (Box-folder 16 / 22-27)
  - #238-4 Press releases (School of Mines), 1936-1941 (Box-folder 17 / 1-3)
  - #238-4 Newspaper clippings and news notes (School of Mines), 1923-1947 (Box-folder 17 / 4-5)
  - #238-5 Newspaper clippings and news notes (Experiment Station), 1928 (Box-folder 17 / 6)
  - #238-6 Newspaper clippings and news notes (Extension Service), 1919-1926 (Box-folder 17 / 7)
  - #238-7 Newspaper clippings and news notes (Chancellor's Office), 1929 (Box-folder 17 / 8)
  - #238-8 Newspaper list, 1922 (Box-folder 17 / 9)
  - #238-8 Newspaper clippings and news notes (Eastern Montana College), 1960 (Box-folder 17 / 10)
  - #238-9 Newspaper clippings and news notes (Northern Montana College), 1930-1961 (Box-folder 17 / 11)
  - #249-12 Intermountain Union College [Montana Wesleyan], 1920-1929 (Box-folder 17 / 12)
  - #255 Surveys (general), 1924-1955 (Box-folder 17 / 13-15)
  - #255-1 Surveys (Farm Success Survey, Extension Service), 1922-1924 (Box-folder 17 / 16)
  - #255-2 Surveys (Montana Educational Survey), 1927-1934 (Box-folder 17 / 17-22)
  - #256 University Fund Campaign (clippings), 1920 (Box-folder 17 / 23)
  - #256 University Bonds (daily logs on construction of Shop, Biology Building, Gymnasium, and Engineering Building), 1921-1922 (Box-folder 17 / 24-25)
  - #256 University Bonds (building contracts), 1921-1922 (Box-folder 18 / 1)
  - #256-1 University Funds Campaign, 1919-1928 (Box-folder 18 / 2)
  - #256-10 University Bonds (litigation), 1921 (Box-folder 18 / 3)
  - #256-11 University Bonds (sale), 1920-1930 (Box-folder 18 / 4)
  - #256-12 University Bonds (referendum 29), 1926 (Box-folder 18 / 5)
  - #256-13 University Bonds (referendum 33 and 34), 1929-1930 (Box-folder 18 / 6-8)
  - #256-14 Taxes (fraternity and sorority houses), 1928 (Box-folder 18 / 9)
  - #256-16 University funds (referendum 42 and initiative 44), 1940 (Box-folder 18 / 10)
  - #263-9 Religious affiliations with or establishment at State educational institutions, 1926-1927 (Box-folder 18 / 11)
  - #263-13 The Montana Study [see also MC 270], 1948-1954 (Box-folder 18 / 12)
  - #263-30 The Montana Study (correspondence), 1944-1949 (Box-folder 18 / 13-19)
  - #263-30 The Montana Study (payroll), 1944-1947 (Box-folder 18 / 20)
  - #263-30 The Montana Study (travel authorizations), 1946-1947 (Box-folder 18 / 21)
  - #263-30 The Montana Study (day book), 1944-1947 (Box-folder 19 / 1)
  - #263-30 The Montana Study (Vol. 1-3), 1944-1947 (Box-folder 19 / 2-4)
  - #266-8 Irrigation projects in Montana along the Great Northern Railway, circa 1922 (Box-folder 19 / 5)
  - #267-2 Extension Service (county agents), 1925 (Box-folder 19 / 6)
  - #267-14 Extension Service (livestock projects), 1921-1924 (Box-folder 19 / 7)
  - #267-20 Extension Service (Junior Farm Bureau Camp), 1920-1921, 1927 (Box-folder 19 / 8)
  - #267-21 Extension Service (Farmers' Week), 1924 (Box-folder 19 / 9)
  - #267-23 Extension Service (Federal Seed Loans), 1921 (Box-folder 19 / 10)
  - #267-24 Extension Service (monthly newsletter), 1922 (Box-folder 19 / 11)
  - Chambers of Commerce and commercial clubs, 1920-1924 (Box-folder 19 / 12)
  - Distribution of high school students and graduates, circa 1933-1934 (Box-folder 19 / 13)
  - Farragut Naval Training Station (conference), 1946 (Box-folder 19 / 14)
  - Index to bulletins, circulars, publications, 1895-1960 (Box-folder 19 / 15)
  - Insurance, 1932 (Box-folder 19 / 16)
  - C.W. Leaphart, Law School Dean (re pictures of Supreme Court justices), 1934 (Box-folder 19 / 17)
  - Montana Conference on Soil Mechanics and Foundation Engineering, 1966 (Box-folder 19 / 18)
  - National Parks Association, 1923-1925 (Box-folder 19 / 19)
  - Newspaper publicity (Greater University, State College, Experiment Station, Extension Service, Eastern Montana College, School of Mines, Northern Montana College, Normal College, State University), 1943-1945 (Box-folder 19 / 20-28)
  - Northern Montana College (report), 1951 (Box-folder 19 / 29)
  - Northern Plains Conference, 1943 (Box-folder 19 / 30)
  - Dr. Eugene S. Perry, "Artesian well areas of Eastern and Central Montana", 1930 (Box-folder 19 / 31)
  - Programs (commencements and public exercises), 1918-1943 (Box-folder 20 / 1-4)
  - Referendums 51, 52, 61 (re University mill levy), 1948, 1958 (Box-folder 20 / 5-8)
  - Research at Montana State College, 1961 (Box-folder 20 / 9)
  - Taxation (reports, court papers, articles), 1931-1933 (Box-folder 20 / 10)
  - Payne Templeton, "What is the High School For?" (re Flathead County high school), 1932 (Box-folder 20 / 11)
  - Francis Thomson article on placer mining, 1929 (Box-folder 20 / 12)
  - University (Military Dept.), 1935, circa 1960 (Box-folder 20 / 13)
  - University (President McFarland resignation), 1958 (Box-folder 20 / 14)
  - University (President Simmons hearings), 1940 (Box-folder 20 / 15)
  - University System (staff salaries), 1938-1949 (Box-folder 20 / 16)
  - War Dept. (appropriations), 1933 (Box-folder 20 / 17)
  - White House Conference on Child Health and Protection, 1931 (Box-folder 20 / 18)
  - Miscellany, undated (Box-folder 20 / 19)